Vincent

Email	thisoneis4business@gmail.com
Mobile	+64273202935
Linkedin	Vincent
Github	<u>d-exclaimation</u>

Personal Statement

I am an enthusiastic and career driven person wanting to get into the technology industry. I would like to apply my software engineering skills to build useful applications that can improve many lives.

Personal Skills

Problem Solving

Learned to solve issues by understanding and breaking down problems when building many difficult projects

Willingness to learn

Motivated to keep learning by building projects outside work and study

Technical Skills

Node.js (with Typescript)

- Built responsive and interactive web application in React
- · Build many GraphQL servers with Node.js
- · Build plenty of complex full stack monorepo applications
- Worked on many Node.js microservices at Partly

Elixir

• Built many realtime capable backend servers using WebSockets

PostgreSQL

• Used PostgreSQL as database of many side projects

Teamwork

Contributed and collaborated in actively-maintained open-source projects

Collaborated in many group projects as part of a university course

Worked in a fast moving and growing team at Partly

Swift

- · Built many highly interactive iOS applications
- · Contributed to an open-source GraphQL schema library in Swift
- Developed and maintained an open-source, spec-compliant GraphQL server library with realtime capabilities in Swift

С

 Developed a multiplayer game in a microcontroller as part of university assignment which achieved full marks

Java

 Developed a GUI game using object oriented design as part of a university assignment which achieved high marks

Work Experience



Software Engineer Intern

November 2022 - February 2023

Worked on marketplace integrations by developing microservices using Typescript, Node.js, GraphQL, React, Angular, and PostgreSQL



Software Engineer

February 2021 - November 2021

Worked on building their online <u>attendance recording application</u> for staff and admins using Typescript, Node.js, GraphQL, React, and PostgreSQL

Vincent 1

Project Experience



Pioneer GraphQL

An open-source, spec-compliant, GraphQL server library for server-side Swift that is GraphQL over HTTP and GraphQL over Websocket capable



Tetr-a-gone

A multiplayer game for the UC Funkit 4 written in as part of UC ENCE260-2022 assignment (Final grade: A+)



dexclaimation.com

A server-side personal website that show my short porfolio, projects showcase, and some fun easter eggs built with Next.js, GraphQL, Go



<u>Flatliner</u>

A 2D shooting platformer game built with Unity and C#

Echoppe

A realtime web and mobile shopping organiser built with React, React Native, and Elixir Phoenix all in a single monorepo with Yarn Packages



CardJitsuClone

An iOS version of the game from Club Penguin Card-jitsu using the MVVM pattern built with Swift and SwiftUI



Education



University of Canterbury

2021 - Ongoing

Studying Bachelor of Science, Computer Science and have been awarded 2nd year scholarship in University of Canterbury

Vincent 2